For top quality or consistent performance, just
remember the name Silver Pump. There were
two stocks of ICBC that
showed results yesterday, one ICBC Prudential
Life Insurance and one ICBC Lombard
General Insurance. Today, we see a
contrarian impact in both of them.
ACI Prudential is up 4% while
General Insurance is down 3%
.  If we look at the results, the
[ __ ] of ACI Prudential Insurance has fallen by 3.1%, which was actually
less than the estimate.  The value of new business
increased by 2.5%, but the
figure is slightly lower than expected.  The value of new business
margin has seen a slight increase
and the company has declared a dividend.
While we have seen more deterioration in general insurance,
especially in
operating profit, which has declined by 26%,
and maybe for the same reason, if we look at the stock today, it will be
negative 3%.
So sir, how are you looking at the
results of both the companies,
how are you looking at the company's results and
how will you keep an eye on the results of both the stocks?
Sir, definitely, yesterday
we were more bullish on ICC Lobd
comparatively, but today when we look at the
reaction in the stock after the results, it seems that there is no good
sign of a bullish trend for ICC Lobd in the market at the moment. Same as if
we look at ECC Life, the chart has become quite
strong
.
Sorry, we should have opened above 50 on the chart level
today.  In the half-
hour session that we have started today, we are
seeing continuous trading near the high.
Volume activity
is also super bullish.  So, looking at the way the chart is
setup today, I feel
that ic life insurance is comparatively
better than ic lombard.  So I
correct myself, I think that Aussie
Life Insurance can
provide a good opportunity for investors from here
and if you want to
create a position in this with a stop loss of 575, then the levels of 640 to 50 above can
come within one to two weeks
.